Shubham Kamath

Software Engineer

github.com/shubhaemk

Dhankawadi, Pune shubhamkamaths@gmail.com 8600074579

linkedin.com/in/shubham-kamath/ shubhaemk.github.io/portfolio/ dev.to/shubhamk

SUMMARY

An innovative thinker, initiative taker and multi dimensional professional, having experience as a Software Developer with Panorbit involved in the development of Company's Products, various Web development and App development projects, while working with developers across the stack.

SKILLS

Front-end HTML5. CSS3, JavaScript, Babel, Webpack

Libraries / React.js,

Frameworks React Native

State Redux, Management Redux-Saga

Recoil

CSS Bulma, **Frameworks Bootstrap**

Database Realm

Version control **GIT**

Cloud **AWS EC2**

EXPERIENCE

Panorbit, LLC - Junior Software Developer January 2020 - Present

As a Software Developer I worked on Front End projects using React and React Native.

Veritas Technologies LLC- Intern January 2019 - June 2019

As an Intern I worked on developing a DDI - Portal for internal use at the company.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Compux : Generate React Components Technologies: Node, NPM, Webpack, Babel

npmjs.com/package/compux

Another React Boilerplate

Technologies: JavaScript, Webpack, Babel

github.com/shubhaemk/another-react-boilerplate

GitCard: Generate Github Profile cards

Technologies: ReactJS, Bulma, Redux

shubhaemk.github.io/gitcard/

Code Indent - Indents Basic Code

Technologies: JavaScript, CSS, Webpack, Babel

shubhaemk.github.io/code-indent/

EDUCATION

MIT - WPU, Pune 2017 - 2019 Master of Science (MSc.), Computer Science

LANGUAGES

- ★ English
- **★** Konkani
- **★** Hindi
- ★ Marathi